你们有没有听说 有个研究小组
Have you guys heard about this research team
试图对鸡的DNA进行转基因处理
that's trying to transgenically manipulate chicken DNA
创造出一种恐龙鸡?
to create some sort of chicken dinosaur?
哦 我觉得这很棒
Oh, I think that sounds wonderful.
什么? 你两个都怕的
What? You're afraid of both dinosaurs and chickens.
对啊 但别告诉我
Yes, but tell me
一个恐龙鸡沙拉三明治
a dinosaur chicken salad sandwich
没有中生代的感觉
wouldn't hit the Mesozoic spot.
- 嘿 各位  - 你好呀
- Hey, guys. - Hey. Hello.
明晚安排没变吧?
We still on for tomorrow night?
当然 终于能见到你女朋友了 我很兴奋
Yeah. I'm excited to finally meet your girlfriend.
是呀 说到这个
Yeah, oh, and speaking of which.
根据牛津大学最近的一项研究表明
According to a recent study out of Oxford University,
每当一个人有了
when someone takes on
新的浪漫对象
a new romantic partner,
就会失去一到两个亲密朋友
that person loses one or two close friends.
你什么时候开始读社会科学的东西了?
Since when do you read social science?
我跟其他人一样 也得上厕所呀
I go to the bathroom like everybody else.
为什么我谈恋爱
Why would I lose friends
就会失去朋友呢?
just because I started dating someone?
对呀 你和Amy谈上的时候 就没失去朋友
Yeah, you didn't lose anyone when you met Amy.
是没有 但研究说的是浪漫对象
Yeah, well, no, the study refers to romantic partners.
我和Amy可不属于这个范畴
Not the way I would categorize the two of us.
可你们也会亲嘴牵手
You guys kiss and hold hands.
我看到他怎么做的 一点都不浪漫
I've seen him do it. It's not romantic.
听着 我不是那种
Look, I'm not the kind of guy
有异性没人性的家伙
who drops his friends just because he's in a relationship.
如果她不喜欢我们怎么办?
What happens if she doesn't like us?
嘿 你们是我的好朋友
Well, hey, you're my dear friends.
刚开始几年你们会收到圣诞卡片
You'll get a Christmas card for a couple of years,
之后就会彻底不联系了
and then you're dead to me.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季第4集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调&时间轴: 。沫   校对: UU爆炸了
翻译: 影子 猫呗 凤梨酥 千欲
Stuart还和你妈妈住一起吗 Howard?
So, Howard, is Stuart still living with your mom?
我不想谈这个话题
I don't want to talk about it.
- 但他还是会抱怨  - 我妈帮他装了有线!
- But he's going to.  - My mom got him cable!
我这一生
In my whole life,
在那房子里长大... 也没有线看
growing up in that house... no cable.
你知道那蚂蝗
Do you know how many HBOs
让我妈给他装了几个HBO台? 七个
that leech had my mother get him? Seven.
七个HBO台 七个!
Seven HBOs. Seven!
长话短说 他们装了七个HBO台
Long story short, they have seven HBOs.
嘿 各位
Hey, guys.
- 嘿  - 你好
- Hey.  - Hello.
- Emily 大多数你都认识了  - 嗨
- Emily, you know almost everybody here.  - Hi.
这是Leonard 这是Penny
This is Leonard, this is Penny.
见到你很高兴
Oh, it's so nice to meet you.
- 彼此彼此  - 嗨
- Nice to finally meet you, too.  - Hi.
你好
Hello.
Raj 她的事你没骗我们呀
Well, Raj, you were not lying about her.
我就说她是真人
I told you she exists.
嘿 我听说你是皮肤科医生
Hey, I hear you're a dermatologist.
对 我在Huntington医院工作
Uh, yeah, I'm a resident at Huntington Hospital.
我喜欢他们的急救室
Oh, I like their emergency room.
没错 哪怕我没有得天狗热
Yeah, even if it turns out you don't have Dengue fever,
他们还是会给棒棒糖吃
they still let you take a lollipop.
要知道 Panny刚开始接受
You know, Penny just started training
医药销售代表的培训
to be a pharmaceutical sales rep.
也许她能和你练习一下
Maybe she can practice on you some time.
我想在真正的医生身上试手会比较好
Oh, it would be great to practice on a real doctor.
我想应该没问题的
Yeah. I'm sure that'd be fine.
我屁股上长了些奇怪的斑点
I have some odd freckles on my buttocks.
我能预约个时间 让你帮忙看看吗?
Can I make an appointment for you to look at them?
呃... 我想可以吧
Um... okay, I guess.
我和他在一起三年 什么都没看着
I'm with him three years, nothing.
她才来了两分钟 他就想脱裤子了
She's with two minutes, and he's taking his pants off.
昨晚真有趣 你觉得Emily怎么样?
Last night was fun. What did you think of Emily?
我不知道
I don't know.
我有种感觉 她不喜欢我
I kind of got the sense she didn't like me.
她说不喜欢你了吗?
Did she say she didn't like you?
当然没说 没人会当着
Of course not. No one ever says
对方的面说不喜欢她
they don't like you straight to your face.
我们的经历太不一样了
We have led different lives.
你们刚认识 她怎么会那么想?
You guys just met. Why would she feel that way?
这只是我的感觉罢了
It's just this vibe I got.
肯定是你想太多了
I'm sure you're worried about nothing.
对 也许你说得对
Yeah. You're probably right.
我以前觉得高中体育老师
I used to think my high school P.E. teacher
不喜欢我 结果却是
didn't like me, but it turned out,
她太过喜欢我了
she liked me a little too much.
- 真的?  - 对呀
- Really?  - Yeah.
不过没事
It was fine.
我们一起听了Melissa Etheridge的音乐会 我拿了A
We went to a Melissa Etheridge concert, I got an A,
结果都是好的
it all worked out.
等你去Emily办公室练习的时候就会发现 没事的
When you go to Emily's office to practice, you'll see. It's fine.
我希望你是对的
Yeah, I hope you're right.
你真的这辈子
You really went your entire life
都没遇到别人当面说"我讨厌你"?
without anyone saying "I hate you" to your face?
对呀
Yeah.
我现在很想说 但你的颧骨太可爱了
I'd say it now, but look at those cheekbones.
我好想念Stuart的店
I miss Stuart's place.
吵杂的音乐和暴露在外的墙砖
All this loud music and exposed brick.
这到底是个漫画店
What, is this a comic book store,
还是三只小猪的围栏?
or a rave at the third little pig's house?
我真希望Stuart能重新开张
Yup, I wish Stuart would reopen.
我也讨厌这个地方
I hate this place, too.
好吧 我相信他说的话
Okay, him I believe
因为他是个穿着青少年T恤的怀旧老头子
because he's an 80-year-old man in a 15-year-old's T-shirt.
但你只是在生
But you're just upset
Stuart 你妈妈和那些HBO有线电视台的气
about Stuart and your mom and all their HBOs.
是的 我现在甚至在看"权利的游戏"时
Yes, I am. You know, I can't even watch Game of Thrones now
脑海里都有我妈的吼声
without thinking of mother saying,
"Stuart 谁是权利啊?"
"Stuart, which one is Thrones?"
他可能不会重新开张了
You know, he might not reopen.
他没从保险公司那拿到多少钱
He didn't get a lot of money from the insurance company.
我的天 只有一样东西能让我火大的话
Oh, boy, if there is one thing that gets my goat,
那就是那帮保险公司的小兔崽子
those dad-gum insurance companies.
为什么? 他们拽着您老的胡子不放?
Why? Because they won't get off your lawn?
哦 那Stuart有没有试着去贷款 或者...或者找投资商?
Oh, is Stuart trying to get a loan, or-or find investors?
我只知道 他让我妈给他
All I know is, he's got my mother
买了超厚卫生纸 真的 四层加厚的
buying four-ply toilet paper. I mean, four-ply.
他的屁股如此娇嫩
If his butt is so delicate,
为什么不买只长毛兔擦屁股?
why doesn't he just use an angora rabbit?
首先 它们会掉毛还会咬人
For starters, they shed and bite.
嘿
Hey,
我有个办法
here's a thought.
我们几个人凑钱补上Stuart还需要的资金
Why don't we put up the rest of the money that Stuart needs?
那这样 我们就是 漫画书店的股东了?
So, we'd be, like, owners of a comic book store?
有种梦想成真的感觉
It's kind of a dream come true.
听起来真不错
That does sound fun.
噢 说不定我们还可以
Ooh, maybe we could come up
制定商业计划来和这家店竞争
with a business plan to compete with this place.
我现在就给你制定计划
I'll give you a plan right now.
第一步: 开一家漫画书店
Step one: open comic book store.
第二步: 开始散播谣言
Step two: start rumor
这家书店会让你得生殖器疣
this comic book store gives you genital warts.
第三步: 买个大袋子装钱
Step three: buy a big bag to put the money in.
这主意还不赖
It's not that bad.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
太感谢你了 能让我在你这练习推销
Thank you so much for letting me practice my sales pitch on you.
真的很感谢
I really appreciate it.
没事
Sure.
嗯 我买了咖啡
Um, I brought coffee.
我不知道你喜欢什么 所以我买了
I wasn't sure what you like, so I got
普通的 卡布奇诺的 还有香料茶
a regular, a cappuccino and a Chai tea.
你喜欢Raj 我想你可能会喜欢香料茶
Since you like Raj, I thought you might be into that.
谢谢 我们可以开始了吧 我有点忙
Thanks. If we could get started. I'm a little busy.
好的 当然 我先把材料拿出来
Oh, yeah, sure. Let me just get out my materials.
这公文包是Leonard送给我的
Leonard gave me this briefcase.
他以前在高中背的
He used to carry it around in high school.
你还能看到包上的凹痕 人家拿这包砸他留下的
You can still see the dent where they whacked him with it.
好吧 我给你介绍
Okay, I would like to talk to you
我们的新避孕药 氟美弗拉
about our new birth control pill, Femevra.
不错
Great.
那么 氟美弗拉的三相设计
So, Femevra's triphasic design
能平衡你的荷尔蒙分泌
provides balanced hormonal exposure.
好的
All right.
同样也被证明
It has also been shown to cause
它比其他口服避孕药导致的副作用更少
significantly fewer side effects than other oral contraceptives.
虽然会让你长痘痘 同样 这也是一种
Although it can cause acne, which, if you ask me, kind of
有效的避孕方式
increases its effectiveness as a contraceptive.
真有趣
Funny.
好吧 抱歉 我们之间是不是有误解?
Okay, I'm sorry. Did we get off on the wrong foot?
因为从那天晚上开始 我就有点觉得
Because since the other night, I kind of feel like
你可能对我存在芥蒂
you might have a problem with me.
不 挺好的
No, it's fine.
你确定吗 看起来不是很好啊
Are you sure, because it doesn't seem fine?
好吧
Okay.
你非要说这个问题的话
If you really want to talk about this,
我确实心存芥蒂
I do have a problem.
天哪 告诉我... 我哪做错了?
Oh, my God. Tell me... what did I do?
其实没什么 我只是...
Look, it's nothing. It's just...
Raj告诉我不久前 你俩睡过
Raj told me that a while ago, you two hooked up.
什么?! 他为什么那么说?
What?! Oh, why would he say that?
你们没有吗?
Did it not happen?
好吧 准确来说不算睡过
Well, I wouldn't exactly call it a hook-up.
你们接吻了?
Did you kiss?
是的
Yeah.
你们都裸着?
Were you naked?
是的
Yeah.
那就是睡过了
So, it was a hook-up.
没有
No.
有
Yeah.
那么 我们有什么办法可以增加
So, what are some ways we could set our comic book store
我们漫画店的竞争力?
apart from the competition?
孩子买漫画书 那就这样
Oh, kids buy comic books. It would be great
找个办法让我们店里的孩子比别的店里多
to figure out a way to get more kids in the store.
我小的时候 我就很喜欢去漫画店
You know, when I was a kid, I loved going there,
但是从来搭不到车
but I could never get a ride.
哦 那我们就开辆货车四处转悠带孩子们去漫画店吧?
Ooh, what if we got a van and drove around and picked kids up?
好主意
Nice.
你的意思是 就像去公园和学校那样?
You mean, like at parks and schools?
玩具店 宠物展
Toy stores, puppet shows.
等等 你们的主意是要弄一辆货车
Hold on. So, your idea is to get a van
在大街上找搭车的孩子?
and cruise the streets looking for kids to pick up?
是的
Yes.
然后要用糖引诱他们上车?
And are you gonna use candy to lure them in?
你不说我们还想不到呢!
We are now!
你告诉Emily我们睡过?!
You told Emily we hooked up?!
要我说 我告诉了所有人
Um, well, in my defense, I tell everybody.
你为什么这么说?!
Why would you say that?!
那时候我们在说前任的问题
We were having a conversation about past lovers.
我们没有谈过恋爱! 拜托
We weren't lovers! Come on.
每个人都知道我们没有上床
Everyone knows we didn't sleep together.
我们只是喝醉了犯傻
We got drunk and fooled around.
为什么你要扯上我呢?
Why couldn't you just leave me out of it?
我们都坦诚相告
Well, we were being honest.
那你甩了Leonard之后
You would leave me out of the conversation
和下一任也不会提起我吗
with the next guy if you dump Leonard?
- 说这个干嘛?  - 是的!
- Why say it?  - Yes!
我不会把你在我的恋爱史上排除掉的
Well, I would never leave you off my list,
而且
and not just
因为 没有你的话
because, without you,
我的恋爱好像就没有"史"了
we're playing fast and loose with the word "list".
干得漂亮 现在她讨厌我了
Well, good job. Now she hates me.
哦
Oh.
这下好了
Great.
至少 牛津大学的研究是对的
On the bright side, that Oxford study was right.
你已经少了一个朋友了
One friend down.
真想知道下一个会是谁
I wonder who you're going to lose next.
是你 行了吧? 就是你了 我们... 友尽!
You, okay? It's you. You're... you're next!
才不会呢 你那么喜欢我
No. You're crazy about me.
真不明白Emily为什么这么在意这件事
I don't know what Emily's so upset about anyway.
就算我和他上过床 那又怎样? 每个人都有过去啊
Even if I had slept with him, so what? Everyone has a past.
大多数人都有过去
Almost everyone has a past.
别这样 你这么漂亮
Come on, look how pretty you are.
她肯定不是第一个讨厌你的女孩
I'm sure this isn't the first girl to hate you.
确实不是
It's not.
你肯定能改变这种状况的
And I'm sure you can turn it around.
怎么改变啊? 你总不能逼着别人喜欢你吧
How? You can't force someone to like you.
不如这样
What if you just
你就假装是她朋友一样和她玩
hang around and act like her friend
直到你的耐心打动她 不知不觉的 你就可以
until you wear her down? I mean, next thing you know,
去她家里 吃她的东西
you're in her home, you're eating her food,
喝她的酒了
drinking her wine.
不行 不靠谱
No, that won't work.
说得对 干杯
You're right. Cheers.
我知道了
Oh, I know.
何不试试用你学过的销售知识
Why don't you use your sales training
回去推销你自己呢?
to go back down there and sell yourself?
- 什么?  - 没错
- What?  - Yeah.
只不过这次卖的不是药
But instead of selling a drug,
而是Penny... 多可爱啊
you'd be selling Penny... it's cute.
多蠢啊
It's stupid.
好吧 你要是不这样 直接否定别人的意见的话
Well, maybe people would like you more
就没那么招恨了
if you didn't crap all over their ideas.
我觉得Penny说得对
I'm gonna go with Penny on this one.
为什么不呢? 我们这么多年的好朋友了
Then again, why wouldn't I? I mean, we go way back.
天啊 我以前根本都不喜欢你
Oh, my God. I didn't used to like you.
嘘 Amy就在你旁边呢
Shh. Amy's here now.
知道吗 我越来越想要
You know, the more I think about it,
真的和你们一起开一家漫画书店了
the more intrigued I am about having our own store.
那样我们就可以
We'll get to see all the new stuff
在新书上架之前就看到内容了
before it hits the shelves.
我们还可以开心的
And we'll get to have fun interactions
和顾客聊天
with our customers.
"这里不是图书馆... 买不买不买滚"
"This isn't a library... buy it or get out."
你其实一直都说这种话的
You say things like that all the time.
是啊 不过我要是店主的话 就有话可以回复
Yes, but as a store owner, I'll finally have a good comeback
"这又不是你的地盘... 闭嘴吧"
to, "You don't work here... shut up."
呃 你知道Penny跟Raj说他不应该把她当做
Uh, do you know how Penny told Raj he should have
- 前任吗?  - 听说了
- left her off his list?  - Yeah.
那你觉得我们讨论这个问题的时候
Well, do you think when she and I had that conversation,
她也藏了些别的前任了吗?
she left people off her list?
肯定的啊
I'm sure she did.
为什么?
Why?
因为如果她没有藏的话
Because if she hadn't,
她说到现在都说不完
she'd still be wading through the list.
你能别说话吗?
Will you stay out of this?
希望Penny也就说过那么几次吧
If only Penny had said that once in a while.
嘿 有什么区别吗?
Hey, what difference does it make?
她想嫁的人是你啊
You're the one she wants to marry.
- 这倒是真的  - 而且我也不确定
- That's true.  - Yeah, and I'm not sure
在二人世界里 完全的坦诚
that complete honesty is always the best thing
是不是最好的选择
for a relationship.
他说得对 有一次 我特别坦诚地告诉Amy
Yeah, he's right. Once, in a moment of candor,
她的头发让我想起
I told Amy that her hair reminded me
浸在油里的鸭子 然后...
of a duck caught in an oil spill. Well...
她摔门而出
she stormed out.
太悲伤了 因为那时候我们正在玩拼词游戏
Which was sad, because we were playing Scrabble,
而我刚刚拿到能拼出"柿子"的字母
and I had all the letters to spell "persimmon."
你插什么嘴?
Why are you even part of this conversation?
你一点都不懂女人
You don't know anything about women.
至少我知道 如果我有老婆或者未婚妻的话
I know that if I had a wife or a fiancée,
像投资漫画书店这样的事
I'd ask her first before I invested money
我一定会问问她的意见的
in a comic book store.
他说得对
He's right.
是啊
Yeah, well,
当然对了
of course I am.
她头发那件事我说的也没错
I was also right about her hair.
除了不会嘎嘎叫
It did everything but quack.
有件事我想听听你的意见
There's something I wanted to run past you.
- 怎么了?  - 呃 我们几个
- What's up?  - Mm, the guys and I
想投资给Stuart的漫画书店
were thinking about investing in Stuart's comic book store.
- 你怎么看?  - 你为什么问我?
- Is that okay?  - Why are you asking me?
我们毕竟订婚了
Well, you know, we're engaged,
而这件事也算是财务方面的大事
and it's kind of a big deal financially.
我觉得还是问问你的意见比较好
It seems like something we should talk about.
这样啊
Oh.
那你觉得成堆的信用卡账单
Well, would you consider mounds of credit card debt
是理财方面的大事吗?
kind of a big deal financially?
是啊
Yeah.
哈
Huh.
那个 我们几个最近在讨论一个
Mm. So, me and the guys were talking about
超赞的投资机会...
this great investment opportunity...
不行
Nope.
你还没听我说完呢
But you didn't hear what it was.
是啊
I know.
别这样嘛
Oh, come on.
好吧 什么计划?
Fine. What is it?
帮Stuart把漫画书店重新开起来
It's to help reopen the comic book store.
不行
Nope.
听我说完啊
Well, hear me out.
Howard 我们在存钱买房呢
Howard, you know we're saving up for a house.
我知道 但是他们几个都想这么干
I know, but all the guys are doing it.
我们四个一起投资 所以也花不了多少钱
We're splitting it four ways, so it's really not that much money.
可是这投资看起来风险有点大
It just seems like a risky investment.
我知道 可是...
I get that. I...
好吧 是这样...
Okay, look...
我那么想投资漫画店是因为...
The reason this is important is...
我父亲离开我和母亲之前...
before my dad left me and my mom...
他经常... 带我去漫画店
he used to... take me to the comic book store.
去漫画店是曾经我和老爸为数不多的回忆之一
It was one of the few things we did together.
Howie 我以前不知道
Oh. Howie, I had no idea.
嗯 我不太想... 不太想说的
Well, I don't... like to talk about it.
哦 宝贝
Oh, baby.
这故事是瞎编的 对吧?
That story's made up, isn't it?
这恰恰说明我是有多想投资漫画店了
That's how much buying a comic book store means to me.
我想就某事问问你的意见
I'd like your honest opinion on something.
当然可以
Of course.
在我说之前
Now, before I start,
我得说我对这件事情非常感兴趣
I need you to know that I'm very excited about this,
你说的任何观点
and anything you say
如果不是热情支持的话
that isn't enthusiastically supportive
可能会极大地影响咱俩的关系
will throw our entire relationship into question.
那么...
So...
别拘束啊
keep an open mind.
我觉得有点小怕怕 Sheldon
I'm feeling a little backed into a corner, Sheldon.
很好 那么...
Perfect. Now...
我打算投资
I'm considering investing
Stuart的漫画店
in Stuart's comic book store.
很有趣
Interesting.
那么你觉得一位成年人
Can you see how a grown man,
并且是很有成就的科学家
an accomplished scientist,
投资到一家商店里
who invests in a store
店里卖的是画册
that sells picture books
画的是穿着五颜六色内裤的飞人...
about flying men in colorful underwear...
这样会不会可能浪费
might be wasting both his financial
他的财力和智力呢?
and intellectual resources?
不会
No.
那么我觉得这点子很棒
Then I think it's a terrific idea.
太好了
Great.
我先给你介绍我们的拉客车
Wait till you hear about our van.
谢谢请我们过来
Thanks for inviting us over.
感谢你们愿意来
Oh, thank you for coming.
听着 Penny 你先别说
Uh, listen, Penny, before you start,
我想为先前在办公室里
I just want to apologize for being so rude
我对你的粗鲁道歉
the other day in my office.
不不 不用道歉
No, no. No need to apologize.
打扰 我能说些话吗?
Excuse me, can I say something?
我真是太爱你俩了
I just love both you guys,
我想让你们好好相处
and I want you to get along.
我说"爱"你 是指朋友的"爱"
And when I say "love" I meant as a friend.
呃 现在表白还过早?
And, uh, way too soon, right?
好 坐下吧 听着 Emily
Okay, sit down. Listen, Emily,
我和Raj之前发生的事
what happened between me and Raj
是很久以前了
was a long time ago.
确实 而且我曾经
It was, and I may have made it seem
把这事太过当真了
like a bigger deal than I should have.
没错 现在我和Leonard在谈恋爱
Yeah, and Leonard and I are engaged now,
我只是希望我们能够一起忘掉这事
and I'm just hoping we can put this whole thing behind us.
我也想这样
Mm. I'd like that, too.
嗯 我想我也没问题
Yeah, I thought I'd be okay with it,
但是当时我看到你那么漂亮
but then I saw how pretty you are.
哦 你嘴真甜
Oh, that's so sweet.
我是说 瞧瞧你 你也很美
I mean, look at you, you are gorgeous.
没错... 你俩都很美
It's true... you're both gorgeous.
是不是侧面说明
Kind of says something about the
能把你们俩都上了的男人...
man who could bed you both.
你现在明白为啥我总是单身了吧
You get why I've been alone most of my adult life.
- 是什么风把你俩吹来了?  - 嗯
- So, what brings you by?  - Well,
我俩来不需要理由... 这是我家
I don't need a reason... it's my house.
严格意义上说 这是你妈家 但...
Technically, it's your mom's house, but...
对你的到来 我们很欢迎
we certainly want you to feel welcome.
我一直很受欢迎
I'm always welcome.
嗯... 下次来之前打个招呼
Mm, just... try and call first.
好吧 先说正经事
Okay, let's get down to business.
Howie考虑给你的漫画店投资
Howie was thinking about putting up some money
帮助你重开店面 但在那之前
to help you reopen the store, but before that happens,
我有几个问题
I have a few questions.
我很感谢你们的帮助
I appreciate the offer,
但是你妈已经把钱给我了
but actually your mother already gave me the money.
什么?
What?
你没听错 我还说给的太多了
Yeah. I told her it was too much,
但是她说他很乐意帮助她的小亲亲
but she said she was happy to help out her bubala.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
妈 你得把那支票撕了
Ma, you are canceling that check,
Stuart不是你的小亲亲 我才是
and Stuart is not your bubala; I'm your bubala.
你不能同时有两个小亲亲!
You can't have more than one bubala!
我不知道他在和谁说话
I don't know who he's talking to.
他妈已经跑到超市 帮我买衣服去了
She's at Target, buying me shirts.
我真是很高兴你俩能和好
I'm so glad we could work this all out.
我也是 你知道吗 我们应该一起
Yeah, me, too. You know, we should have dinner
共进晚餐 带上Leonard
one night with you and Leonard.
哦 那样太好了
Oh, we would love that.
不错!
Great!
- 好吧 晚安  - 好 晚安
- Okay, good night, guys.  - All right, night.
再见
Bye.
- 我讨厌她  - 我讨厌她
- I hate her.  - I hate her.
我对不能拥有自己的漫画店
I'm really disappointed we're not gonna have
感到无比失望
our own comic book store.
我懂
I know.
我原本很期待的
I was looking forward to it.
如果有我们自己的漫画店有多好
It would've been so nice to have a place that was ours,
我们就可以坐下来安静地看书
where we could just sit and read comics in peace.
舒服的座位
With comfy seats.
还有零食
And snacks.
也许这愿望只能想想了
Well, I guess it was too good to be true.
是啊
Yeah.